（早乙女）むかし　男　初冠して
奈良の京　春日の里に→
"Mukashi, otoko, uwikauburishite,
nara no miyako,
Note: The first lines of the Ise Monogatari,
a set of classical Japanese poems
しるしよしして
狩りに往にけり…と。→
kasuga no sato ni, shiruyoshi
shite, kari ni inikeri."
おい　これ　誰か訳してみろ。
Hey, one of you guys try translating that.
（古市）あの　先生
今　世界史の授業ですけど。
Um, Sensei?
It's time for world history right now...
え！？ハハハ！間違えちまった。
Whoops, my mistake.
まあ　いいや。めんどくせえ。
おい　男鹿　お前　訳せ。
Well, who cares? What a pain.
You there, Oga. Translate it.
（男鹿）はあ！？横暴か！
Huh?!
（早乙女）いいから　訳せ！おら！
You're forcing me?
Just translate it!
うえ～。
（ベル坊）アダ！
あ～男があれだ。
う　うり坊に乗って→
A man like, you know...
He got on the back of a wild boar piglet...
奈良に行ったらだな。
ほう？
And headed to Nara, I think?
うっせ！バカ！
日本語しゃべれ！こら。
ダブ！
Oh?
Shut it, idiot!
Try speaking Japanese!
The Sibling Rivalry Has Begun
（古市）あれ？えっと→
Huh? Wha... Crap, I left my cellphone!
うわ～オレ　携帯　置いてきた！
あ？何やってんだよ。バカ市。
What the heck are you doing, stupid-ichi?
うっせ～な。
バカっていう奴がバカ～！
Oh, shut up... People who say
"stupid" are the stupid ones!
ダッシュで取ってくるから
お前　ちょっと待ってろよ！
I'll go get it on the double,
so you just wait right there!
待ってろよ！
はいはい。
Wait there!
Sure, whatever.
絶対　待ってろよ～！
…んだよ。
You'd better wait for me!
ベル坊　コロッケ　がまんだな。
Baby Beel, hold out a bit for that croquette.
アイ。
ん？
（邦枝）聞きたいことがあるの。
I have something I want to ask you.
答えて。その子　一体　何者なの？
Answer me.
Who is that kid, exactly?
何者？ん～と…。
Who is he?
Um...
《どっから説明すりゃいいんだ？
まずは名前か？》
Where should I start?
I guess from his name...
《うん。名前は重要だな。よしっ》
Yup. The name is definitely important.
Okay!
《確か　すげ～長い名前
だったんだよ　え～と→
If I remember right, his
name is super long...
ウンタラカンタラ　ベルウンタラ
みたいな》
Um, like "something something"
Beel "something something"?
《思い出せ！オレ。
ベル…ベル…ベルリン！？》
Come on, remember!
Beel, Beel... Berlin?
あ…あの…男鹿？
Um, Oga?
あ～！ちょっと待って！
もう少しだから！
Wait a sec, just a little bit...
ベル…ベラ…ベロ…。
Beel, Bela, Belo...
《男鹿の子じゃないことは
わかってる→
I know that he's not Oga's kid.
かと言って　ヒルダさんの
子供でもない》
And neither is he Hilda-san's...
《坊っちゃまって言ってたし
じゃあ　この子は一体　何？》
She calls him "Young Master"...
Then who is he, actually?
《どうして　あなたが面倒
みてるの？あの力は一体？》
Why are you taking care of him?
What was that power?
((ゼブルブラスト！))
Zebel Blast!
《それに…ヒルダさん
何あれ》
Plus, Hilda-san...
What was that?
《絶対　普通じゃない。
さあ　白状しなさい！男鹿》
That's not normal, no way.
Now, out with the truth, Oga!
ベ…ベル…ベルマーク！
いや　違うな。
B-Beel... Belmark!
Wait, that's not it.
《これは…！えらい所に
居合わせてしまった～！》
This is... I've stumbled
on a real scene here!
《告白か？告白なのか！？》
Is this a confession?
Could she be confessing?
《百歩　譲って
告白という名のあれか！？》
Is this what they mean by take
100 steps back and confess?
《古市イヤー…イヤーイヤー》
Furuichi Ear!
（邦枝）どうしたの？ただの
赤ん坊じゃないんでしょ？
What's the problem? He's
no normal baby, right?
《これはベル坊のことを
聞いてんのか？》
She's asking him about Baby Beel?
《あれだけ派手にやったもんなぁ。
怪しんで当然だよな→
Well he did do a real number back then...
Guess it's only obvious she'd get suspicious.
って　おいおいおい！どうすんだ！？
男鹿。ついに秘密をバラすのか！？》
Which means... Hey, what're
you gonna do, Oga?
Is the jig finally up?
悪魔だの魔王だの
言っちゃうのか～！？→
You gonna blab about the Demons
or Demon Lords and whatnot?
ていうか　お前
ちゃんと説明できんのか！？》
And besides... Can you even explain properly?
だぁぁ！面倒くせえ！ベル坊！→
God, what a pain!
Baby Beel, answer her yourself!
お前　自分で答えろ！
ニョ！？
《ベル坊に　ぶん投げた！》
He totally bailed to the Beel!
アア…。
ああ…。
アッア…だ。
だ？
Da?
だ。
だ…。
Da.
Da?
「だ」じゃねえええ！
おお　古市。
Da... not!
Oh, Furuichi.
バカか！？バカなんですか！？
「だ」じゃね～だろ！？
Are you an idiot? Are you a total idiot?
Da ain't gonna cut it!
何　強引に説明しきったみたいな
空気　出してんだ！ぼけ！！
Why're you acting like you actually
explained anything, blockhead?!
邦枝先輩も　きぜんと
突っ込んでくださいよ！
Kunieda-senpai, don't let
them get away with that!
放っておいたら　そいつら
どこまでもカオスですよ！
You let that slide, and god knows
what chaos they'll devolve into!
え　ええ…。
いいとこ来た！
Uh, okay?
Great timing!
こいつの名前なんだっけ？
アダ！
What was his name again?
そこから～！？ほら！もう
ありえないでしょ！？
That was the sticking point?
There's no way you believe it, right?
そもそも　こいつに
聞くとこから間違ってんすよ！
Your mistake was asking those
guys in the first place!
あなた　知ってるの！？
もちろん！
You know?
But of course!
アダ！
この子の名前はカイゼル…→
His name is Kaiser...
ん？カイベル…ゼ？あれ？
カイベルゼバブ４世？あれ？
Kaibeel... ze... huh?
Kaibeelzebub the 4th?
違うな…え～と。
あ…あぶ。
No, that's not it...
わかった！ベルボトム３世！
ジーパンの国の王子か。
I know... Bellbottom the 3rd!
The Prince of the Denim Kingdom?
え？じゃあ　ベルボーイ３世？
偉いのか？偉くないのか。
Then, Bellboy the 3rd?
Is that a high position or not?
ベルギーワッフルって
おいしいよね！
Belgian waffles sure are tasty!
確かに　おいしいが
もはや　それは　ただの感想だ！
That is definitely true, but we're
just brainstorming now, aren't we?
よ～し！じゃあ　全部まとめて→
Great! Then putting it all together...
ベルマーク・カイベルゼバブ・ベルボトム＆ベルボーイ
かつベルギーワッフル３５世でどうだ！
How about Belmark Kaibeelzebub Bellbottom
& Bellboy plus Belgian Waffle the 35th?!
ア　アイー！
え　いや　どうだって言われても！
What? I don't get...
どんだけ適当なんだ！お前は！
You just make it up as you go along, huh?
なんだよ！偉そうなこと言って→
Get off your high horse! You forgot it, too!
てめ～も忘れてんじゃね～か！
何がカイベルだ！
Kaibeel my ass!
キイー。
（古市）ど　ど忘れだよ！
だって　よく考えたら→
Well, excuse me! We've only
heard his full name like, twice!
こいつのフルネームなんて
２回しか聞いたことないじゃん！
もうワッフルでいいじゃん！
ヒッヒッアーダブ！イヤー！
Let's just call him Waffle!
お　男鹿！１５メートル！
あ～！マズイ！
Oga, 15 meters!
Oh, crap!
《そりゃ怒るわよ》
Yeah, that'd make him angry.
（ヨルダ）
カイゼル・デ・エンペラーナ・
ベルゼバブ４世よねえ。
Kaiser Emperana Beelzebub the 4th, yes?
ア…。
（ヨルダ）
よしよし…ダメよ。大魔王様の
息子が簡単に泣いたりしちゃ。
There there... You mustn't go making
the Great Demon Lord's son cry.
（男鹿・古市）あ？
ヒルダさん？
Hilda-san?
失礼な男ね。あんなゲス女と
一緒にしないで下さる？
You are such a rude man.
Please don't place me on par with that wench.
うっ！
古市！
ダブ！
Furuichi?
アウ？
うっ！
ふ～ん。
あなたが男鹿辰巳くん？
あっ！
So you are Oga Tatsumi-kun?
ごめんなさいね。
男鹿！
I'm sorry...
Oga!
死んで下さる？
Would you please die?
ひょ！
あっあ…。
ケホケホ！いやあね。埃まみれに
なっちゃったじゃない。
How horrid... Now I've gotten all dusty.
相変わらず色気のない
登場だこと。
Always with the unsexy entrances, you are.
（ヨルダ）ヒルダ。
（ヒルダ）ヨルダ　なぜ　貴様が
ここにいる？
Hilda...
Yolda.
Why are you here?
ああら　何も聞いてないの？
かわいそ。
What, you hadn't heard?
Poor thing.
というか
あなた　すでにボロボロね。
Or wait, you're already quite beat up.
ヨルダ？
ヒルダ！てめえ　一体…！
Yolda?
Hilda, what the hell?
坊っちゃまを連れて下がっていろ。
こいつの目的は私だ。
Take the Master and stand back.
She's after me.
（ヨルダ）
あらあらあら　つれなぁい。
Oh? That's such a shame...
数年ぶりの再会だって
いうのに　もうお別れ？
It's been so many years since our last
reunion, and we have to part so soon?
（イザベラ）おやめなさい！→
Stop this at once!
勝手な行動は慎みなさい。ヨルダ。
Refrain from any personal actions, Yolda.
あなたとヒルデガルダの因縁は
存じています。
I am aware of your history with Hildegarde.
…が　今は　その時では
ありません。
But now is not the time.
あ…。
（ヨルダ）でもでもイザベラ。→
But, but... Isabella...
（サテュラ）慎め！ヨルダ！
Have some sense, Yolda!
サテュラは黙ってなさいよ。
何ぃ！
Satura, you be quiet!
Say, what?
（焔王）
よい。三人とも下がっておれ。
Enough! The three of you, stand back!
おっと。
Oh...
ああ…。
ヒルダ　何ボサっとしてるの。
ひざまずきなさいよ。
Hilda, what are you standing there
for? Get down on your knees.
焔王様　見つけました。
ベルゼ様でございます。
Lord En, we have found him.
This is Beelze-sama.
シッ！つ～か　あの契約者
弱そうっすよ？
Man, that person he's
contracted with looks weak!
あなたは…！
You're...
（焔王）久しぶりじゃのう。
Long time no see, little brother.
弟よ。
（焔王）久しぶりじゃのう。弟よ。
弟！？まさか。
Little brother?
Don't tell me...
You were a guy all along?
お前　男だったのか。
ずいぶん　ちっちゃい兄貴だな。
And for an older brother he's quite dinky.
このクソたわけが！
なあああ！
You wretched imbecile...
焔王様…坊っちゃまの兄君だ。
This is Lord En... The
Master's older brother.
ベル坊の？いたのかよ。んなもん。
Baby Beel's? Don't remember him having one...
ダアア。
フン！イザベラ。
はい　坊っちゃま。
Isabella!
Yes, Master...
あっ！
アマチャボウイブホル…。
魔言召喚トリックアート。
Demonword Summon Trick Art!
W-What? A piece of paper
turned into a big chair?
な　なんだ！？紙切れから
でっかい椅子が！？
ふっふっふ…。
何をする気だ。
What are you here to do?
ふっふっふっふ。
はっはっはっはっは！
は～っはっはっはっは！
よっこい…よっこい…→
Here... Here...
よっこいしょ～いち
しょ～いち→
Here come de judge!
しょ～いち　しょ～いち…。
Yolda, I would like to be cooled.
ヨルダ　あおぐがよい。
はぁい　坊っちゃま。
As you wish, Master.
は～快適。サテュラ　いつもの。
Ah, that hits the spot.
Satura, the usual.
へ～い　メロンソーダっす！
Righto! Here's your melon soda!
（ズズーッ）
というワケでな。
So you see...
余は焔王。その赤子の兄じゃ。
I'm Lord En, the brother of this baby.
We already got that!
聞いたよ　さっき！なんだ　お前！？
今の一連の流れ！
What's with you? Was this
whole deal just for that line?
そのためだけ？ムダすぎんだろ！
Going a bit overboard, aren't we?
Of course!
もちろんじゃ。余は偉いのじゃ。
I am a very important person.
下々のものと
同じペースでは動かん。
I cannot be drawn into the
same pace as some commoners.
当たり前田のクラッカーじゃ。
You bet your sweet bippy!
Oga... Wait a second...
男鹿…ちょっと待って
何なの？今の。
What the heck was that just now?
あん？知らね～よ。魔法か
何かだろ？あいつら悪魔だし。
How the hell should I know? Magic
or something... They're all demons.
ま　魔法！？悪魔！？
Magic? Demons?
I've told you before... He's
a demon, and so is Hilda.
なんだよ。前にも言ったろ？
こいつもヒルダも悪魔だぜ。
《はっ！》
これこれ　そこのもの。
Hold it there, you.
無関係の人間に教えては　いかん。
You can't go telling humans
that aren't involved.
そちは弟の契約者であろう？
ならば人間を滅ぼす側の人間じゃ。
You're the one my brother has
the contract with, right?
That makes you a human
that'll wipe out the humans.
は…。
（焔王）それともそのメスに情でも
あるのか？
Or do you have feelings for that female?
あ？
（ヨルダ）いいえ　坊っちゃま→
That's not it, Master. It's the
girl who has feelings for him.
情があるのは
あっちの娘の方ですわ。
ほう～！お前は
そういうの鋭いのう！
Oh! You're so perceptive
about these things, Yolda.
先ほどなど　私が　あの男に
キスしようとしたら→
She got all serious when I went
to try and kiss him earlier.
必死になってましたもの。
あっ！
（焔王）ほほう！キスとな！
（ヨルダ）でも全然ウブそうですし→
A kiss, huh?
But he seems totally innocent... Perhaps
she hasn't properly told him yet?
まだ想いも伝えて
ないんじゃないかしら。
H-Hey you! What the heck are you saying?!
ちょちょっとあなた！何
言ってんの！そんなワケないで…。
That's not how it is!
You're cute.
かわいいわね。
はっ！
図星つかれて焦った？
All upset because I hit the mark?
あっ！
邦枝！
Kunieda!
Don't worry, I just knocked
her unconscious like that man.
（ヨルダ）安心なさい。そこの男と同じ
気絶させただけよ。→
今は　まだね。
For now, at any rate.
You bastards... What the
hell have you come for?
てめえら　一体
何しに　きやがった。
お～お～。そう怖い顔をするな。
今日は挨拶に来ただけじゃ。
Don't go makin' such a scary face.
Today I just came to introduce myself.
挨拶？どういうことだよ！
Introduce yourself? What's
the meaning of this?
んっふっふ～そうじゃの～。
Yes, let me see...
うむ…もう少し
落ち着いた所で話さんか？
Hmm, maybe we could talk in a
place that's a bit more cozy?
ここでは　いやじゃ　いやじゃ…。
I don't like this place.
くっ…あいつ　どついていいか？
あ　いや…。
I can punch him, right?
Um, no.
わかったよ　ついてこいや。おお～！
Fine, I get it.
Follow me.
人間　一つだけ
言っておくことがある。
Human, let me tell you just one thing!
When it comes to potato chips,
I go for nori salt flavor!
余は　ポテトチップスは
のりしお派じゃ！
あいつ　ぶっ飛ばして…。
ダー。
Please can I blast him?
No.
で…何でまたオレんち？ねえ　何で！？
So... Why is it my house again?
Tell me why!
Sorry, I didn't have a choice.
すまん　仕方なかったんだ…。
男鹿…。
Oga...
I can't have my own house
get blown up again, right?
オレんちが　ぶっ壊されたりしちゃかなわんだろ。
げげっ！→
You damn well had a choice!
仕方ないって言わねえよ　それ！→
You think you can do whatever the hell
you want when someone is unconscious?
人が気絶してるのをいいことに
やりたい放題か！
Cool, I found a porno mag!
うわぁお　エロ本みっけ！
サテュラ　およしなさい指が腐るわよ。
Satura, put that down at once.
Your fingers will be sullied.
Hey, don't touch that!
（古市）ちょっと！
そこ触んないで！
Brother?
（ほのか）お兄ちゃん…。
このタイミングで…。
Now's not the time...
Take the tea already.
ちょっと　お茶とってよ。
何？この人たち…。
What's with these people?
え？いや　ほら　あの
マカオからの留学生だ。
T-They're like, exchange students from Macao!
Again?
（ほのか）またあ？
あなた…。
You there. What is this?
これは　何ですか？
麦茶ですけど。
Barley tea...
Master only drinks 100% juice.
坊っちゃまは　１００％ジュースしか
お飲みになりません。
And not from concentrate,
either, but freshly squeezed!
それも濃縮還元ではなく
ストレート…。
Ooh, barley tea! Got any sugar?
おお　麦茶か！
砂糖は入っておるのか？
Please bring sugar!
砂糖を持って来なさい。
はあ…。そこの娘。→
Girl there.
Still haven't brought me more potato chips?
ポテトチップスのおかわりは
まだか？のりしおじゃぞ。
Nori salt flavor, got it?
へ？自分で持って来た…。
Go get some yourself!
うわ～っ！え…偉い人だから
そうは見えないけど→
He's a really important person!
He might not look like it...
But he's a really important guy,
so get him some potato chips, 'kay?
実は結構　偉い人らしいから
ポテチ用意して　ねっ！
Sheesh!
も～！
（バタン）
（焔王）
さて…では本題に入るとしよう。
なげえ。
Right then. Let's get down to business.
Longwinded...
Why did I come to the Human World?
何故　余が人間界に来たか。→
And why am I just so cool?
そして何故　余が
こんなにもかっこいいか。
Goddamn he's annoying.
うぜ～がスルー。
（焔王）さぞかし疑問も
つきん事じゃろう。
I bet you're asking yourself those questions.
To explain these things,
それを説明するには　まず→
we should tell you about what's going
on with the Great Demon Lord now.
今の大魔王様のことを
お話しすべきでしょう。
You can't mean... Something has
happened to the Great Demon Lord?
まさか　大魔王様に
何かあったのですか？
実は…。
You see...
Great Demon...
（大魔王）大魔王～！→
Tomorrow I'm gonna destroy the humans!
わし　明日から人間滅ぼす。→
'Cause you know they're like all,
何かさ～　あいつらさ～
今思ったんだけど　ウザくない？→
I'm thinkin', man they're annoying and stuff.
Like, spreadin' and breedin'...
増えすぎってゆっか～　根絶やしにしたら　マジうけるんですけど。
Exterminating them would
be so kick-ass, you know?
Yes, Great Demon Lord...
（側近）ですが　大魔王様。
それでしたら既に→
But you have already dispatched your
youngest son to the Human World for that purpose.
末の息子様を
人間界に遣わしたのですが…。
Oh, did I?
え～　そうだっけ？あっ　そかも…
でもでもでも～　っていうか～→
Maybe I did.
But-but-but, like... he's
sure taking a while.
遅くね？
（側近）え？はあ？
Definitely taking too long, for sure!
（大魔王）遅いよね？ねっ？
なにぶん　まだ赤子ですから。
However he is just a baby, so...
Whatever, I've made up my mind!
Make his older brother do it!
（大魔王）もうあれだ　決めた！
兄貴にやらせよう。→
Lord En!
焔王　アイツだ～！イザベラ
アイツ連れて行って滅ぼせ。なっ。
はい。
Him!
Isabella... Take him and
get to destroyin', you dig?
Yes, my Lord.
あ～！
という訳じゃ。
So there you go!
（男鹿・古市）
大魔王　超テキトーだな…。
あ～。
This Great Demon Lord is such a flake...
Basically I've come here to destroy
humanity under my father's orders.
というわけでの　余も父上の
言いつけで人間を滅ぼしに来たぞ。
Thanks for having me!
よろしくのう。
Actually, no thanks.
いや　よろしくじゃね～よ。
このガキ！
おうっ！何をする。無礼者。
You little brat.
How dare you, ruffian!
This Great Demon Lord is what, an
idiot? The Great Idiot Idiot Lord?
大魔王ってのは　あれか？
アホなのか？
アホアホ大魔王なのか？
He totally forgot about Baby Beel!
完全にベル坊のこと
忘れてんじゃねえかよ。
And letting a baby go destroy humanity?
しかも人間滅ぼすっつって
赤ん坊の次によこしたのが→
This little pisser?
こんな小便くせーガキ…どっ！！
Hilda, what is with this horribly rude thing?
ヒルダ　何？この不快な生き物
さっさと殺しちゃいましょうよ。
《お前が悪い》
Let us kill him at once!
You deserved that.
Stop that, Yolda. I believe he stated we
just came today to introduce ourselves.
やめなさい　ヨルダ。今日は
挨拶だけと言ったはずですよ。
Furthermore, we can kill him any time.
それに殺すのは
いつでもできます。
は～い。
Yes, ma'am...
それで…つまるところ→
In other words, we're being dismissed?
私達は　お払い箱ということ
なのでしょうか？
Ooh, that'd be great!
おうっ！そいつはいいなあ。お前ら帰んのか？いつだ？明日か？
You goin' home?
When? Tomorrow?
（古市）《今のも　お前が悪い…》
You deserved that, too.
あなたらしくありませんね
ヒルデガルダ。
That's not like you, Hildegarde.
Why are you being so weak?
（イザベラ）
何を気弱になっているのです。
魔界屈指の名家に生まれ→
Born to one of the foremost
families in the Demon World,
you should be an elite among
we Demon Maidservants...
我々　侍女悪魔の中でも
トップエリートであった　あなたは→
Aren't you supposed to stand up
resolutely faced with any situation?
いついかなる時でも　毅然と
立っていたではありませんか。→
Do not worry, the Great Demon Lord
did not say anything about that.
安心なさい。
大魔王様は　そのようなこと→
ひと言も　おっしゃっては
おりません。
Indeed. I bet my father didn't
think it through at all.
うむ。父上は恐ろしく
何も考えておらんからな。
This is the time for we brothers
to work together and destroy!
「兄弟同士仲良く滅ぼせ」
そんなところじゃろ。
Oh? I think we should get rid of them!
あら～　私は　お払い箱でいいと思いま～す。
そんなわけで
よろしくの　弟よ。
So let's work well together, brother of mine!
あ　あい！
あ～…やっ！
（イザベラ・サテュラ・ヨルダ）あっ！
は～っ！
あう　あい…えいっ！
うぃ～っ！
ちょっ　坊っちゃま？
何をしておいでですか？
Master!
What are you doing?
あっ！
坊っちゃま！
Master!
ああ…。
にゃっ。
（男鹿・古市）あっ？
えっ…ううっ…。
Hot!
熱っ！
何だ！？
What the...
Master, Yolda is going
to fan while she dances!
坊っちゃま！ヨルダ　踊りながら
あおいじゃいますよ～。
Hilda, you help, too!
ヒルダ！
あんたも手伝いなさいよ！！
Isabella is now going to sing
a song praising her Master!
イザベラ！坊っちゃまを称える歌歌わせて頂きます！
♪～　ラーラー　坊っちゃまは～でっかいな～　大きいな～
La~la~ You're so grand, Master! So big!
Far more important than a potato chip!
♪～　ポテチと比べりゃ
格段に～
な　なんすか？
何で燃えてるんですか？
What is this? Why is he on fire?
Yes... When Lord En throws a tantrum, he
plunges the area around him into a sea of fire.
うむ。焔王坊っちゃまは
癇癪を起こすと→
あたり一体　火の海にしてしまわれるのだ。
And, Baby Beel just made
his older brother cry?
《てゆ～か
ベル坊に泣かされる兄って…》
When Lord En had a big tantrum in the Demon
World, the sea boiled off for 7 days and 7 nights...
以前　魔界で大泣きされた時は
７日７晩消えずに→
魔界の海を干上がらせたからな。
（古市）火の７日間！？
言ってる場合か！
7 days of fire?!
Now's not the time!
W-What'll we do?
ど　ど～すんだよ！？
とにかくなだめるの！
あなた達も歌いなさい！！
Anyway, console him! You all, sing!
Master, you're so grand! So big!
♪～　坊っちゃまは～
でかいな～　大きいな～うえ…。
Look, Master! I bet you'd
love these sneakers!
ほら　坊っちゃまの好きそうな
スニーカーですよ～。
（古市）
うわぁあああ！！
オレの…オレの限定スニーカー！
M-My limited edition sneakers!
The ones I waited for 8 hours in line to buy
because I heard they'd make me cool if I wore them!
これを　はいていれば
モテると聞いて→
８時間並んで
ようやく買ったのに～！
Then how about this?!
こうなったら　これだ～！
がぁあああ！今度は
オレのもしもの時用の　あれが～！！
Now it's the stuff I use when I do that!
あっ…。キモ。
気持ち悪いですね。死ねばいいのに。
Gross.
Disgusting, indeed.
You should just die.
Creepichi.
きもいち。ぶあ～。
何でオレだけ…。
Why me?
This is no time for randomness!
なんてやってる場合じゃ
なかった！
う　う…ん…。
Baby Beel, apologize! Get down
on your knees and apologize!
ベル坊！
謝れ！土下座して謝れ！
あ～いだ　ば～ぶ！
まあ　坊っちゃま！→
Master, what a perfect
somersault! Impeccable!
見事な前転　素晴らしいですわ！
って　違う！！
That's not it!
はっ！そうだ　ゲームだ！おい　そこのキモイの！
はい　キモイのです…。
That's it! Games!
You there, creeper guy!
Yes, creeper guy here.
（サデュラ）
何か人間界のゲーム持ってないか？坊っちゃまは大のゲーム好きだ。→
Do you have some Human World games?
The Master loves games more than anything!
If he sees a Human World game
his attitude is sure to improve!
人間界のゲームを見れば
機嫌もきっと直る！
S-Sure, but...
（古市）あ　あるけど…。
よぉし！
Yes! Master, he said he
has Human World games!
坊っちゃま
人間界のゲームですって！
Behold the skills of our Master!
坊っちゃまの実力
見せたって下さいよ～！
うっ…やる。
I'll play!
Yesss!
（イザベラ・サテュラ・ヨルダ）
おっしゃああああ！！
ははん。言っておくが
余は相当なゲーマーじゃぞ。
I should warn you, I'm quite the gamer.
What system do you have? A
Gigadrive? Super Lolicon?
機種は何じゃ？ギガドライブか？
スーパーロリコンか？
I'll let you power my PC Edison if you want.
今度　余の持っているＰＣエジソンを貸してやってもよいぞ。
Well, we don't have the newest model...
いや～
うち　最新機種ないんですよ。
Oh, but I'm a wiz at retro-games.
よいよい　レトロゲーも得意じゃ。
I'll make you squeal good
before I destroy humanity.
人間界を滅ぼす前に
軽くひねってくれるわ。
W-What kind of system is this?
な　なんじゃ　この機種は…見たことないのう。
I've never seen it before!
There's all kinds of buttons!
ボタンがいっぱいついておる。コントローラーが分厚いではないか！
The controller is really thick!
It's a Playstephanie 2.
プレイステファニー２ですよ。
Playstephanie, got it.
プレイステファニーとな？
えっと　じゃあこれで…。
So, here...
King of Fridays!
Whoa, what's with these realistic graphics?!
なんじゃ！？このリアルな画面は！
だ～！
I'll be the King of Fridays!
「金曜日の覇者はオレだぜ！」
「はてな　いっきま～す！」
Here comes Hathena!
Fight!
「ファイッ！」
（焔王）うわ～！どどど…
どうすればいいんじゃ～！
W-W-What should I do?
Master, good luck!
坊っちゃま～　頑張って！
ファイトです　坊っちゃま！
Fight, Master!
You'll be fine! You're a
genius at games, Master!
大丈夫っすよ　なんたって
坊っちゃまはゲームの天才っすから！
ははは…え～と　このボタンが
小キックで　こっちがガード。
Um, this button is light kick.
This is to block.
If you spin this and press this
button, you'll do a special move.
こう回して　このボタンを押すと
技が出ます。
は～っ　余　すごい！
I'm so awesome!
だ。
What? You wanna play, too?
何だ？お前もやりてえのか？
Master! So gallant!
坊っちゃま　なんと凛々しいお姿！できんのか？
Can you play?
あ～　だぶだ～。
ふん。
I'm not going to hold back just
'cause you're my little brother.
弟とはいえ　容赦はできぬぞ。
ふん。
I'll be the King of Fridays!
「金曜日の覇者はオレだぜ！」
「いくでごわす！」
Here I gowasu!
（ゴング）
「ファイッ！」
（焔王）おりゃ～！
どうだ　これで近づけまい！
Fight!
How 'bout this? Can't get close now!
ふ～　あいたた～！
あいただ～！
くそっ　ならば　これじゃっ！
Then how about this?
あいただ～！
（古市）ドットを読んでいる！？
He's becoming one with the pixels!
Master, how incredible!
坊っちゃま　なんて素晴らしい！
お～　スゲエな。
Yeah, wow...
だ～っ！！
KO!
「ＫＯ！ノーダメージ！」
No damage!
うぃ～っ！
（古市・ヒルダ・男鹿）あ…はっ！！
う…。
（イザベラ・サテュラ・ヨルダ）焔王お坊ちゃま！！
Lord En!
だっ！
いや　だって！
Yeah, but...
That's right! It's not the Master's fault!
そうです　坊っちゃまは悪くありません。
He's just super talented at
games and strong, and cool!
ただ　ちょっとゲームが上手くて
強くて　カッコよかっただけです！
ううう…。
いいから何とかしなさいよ！
Whatever, just do something!
Isabella, Yolda, Satura!
イザベラ　ヨルダ　サテュラ！
（ヨルダ・サテュラ・イザベラ）はい！
Y-Yes?!
We're going to destroy
the Human World, right?
人間界を滅ぼしに行くのですね！
やりましょう　坊っちゃま！
Let's do it, Master!
ううっ…し…知らぬであった！
I-I had no idea!
Eh?
（ヨルダ・サテュラ・イザベラ）え！？
To think the games in the Human
World had progressed so much!
まさか人間界のゲームが
ここまで進んでいようとは…→
A revolution! This is a revolution!
革命じゃ！これは革命じゃよ！
Tomorrow, we're heading to a game shop!
明日　ゲームショップに行く！
人間界を滅ぼすのは　その後じゃ！
We'll destroy the Human World later!
（ヨルダ・サテュラ・イザベラ）
はい…坊っちゃま。
Yes, Master.
だだだ…うい～っ！
あいだだぶ～！
ああ？オレと勝負するってか？
ベル坊。
What, you challenging me, Baby Beel?
Master, you're so cool!
ま～　坊っちゃま　カッコいい！！
（焔王）待て！相手は余がする。
今度こそ返り討ちじゃ。
Wait! I'll be your opponent!
I'll get you back for before!
Lord En, you can do it!
（ヨルダ・サテュラ・イザベラ）
焔王様　ファイトー！
Will you people go home already?
（古市）もう帰れよ　お前ら…。
What's with Baby Beel's brother?
His references are so old!
Who would get "Here come de
judge" in this day and age?
No kidding.
Next episode, that brother of Beel's
is heading to Ishiyama Land!
The screamer coaster, and
the fearful haunted house!
Ishiyama will be covered in a sea of fire!
On the next Beelzebub: His
Brother was a Crybaby!
If that's how it is, we'll have to
lighten his mood with a light joke!
What time is it when an
elephant sits on your fence?
Oops, out of time.